// utils/mockQuiz.js
export const mockQuiz = [
  {
    question: 'What is React Native?',
    options: ['A web framework', 'A mobile app framework', 'A game engine', 'An OS'],
    correctAnswer: 'A mobile app framework',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which language is used in React Native?',
    options: ['Java', 'Swift', 'JavaScript', 'Python'],
    correctAnswer: 'JavaScript',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which company developed React Native?',
    options: ['Google', 'Facebook', 'Microsoft', 'Apple'],
    correctAnswer: 'Facebook',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is JSX?',
    options: ['Java Syntax Extension', 'JavaScript XML', 'JSON Parser', 'None'],
    correctAnswer: 'JavaScript XML',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the default navigation library?',
    options: ['React Navigation', 'Redux Nav', 'RouterX', 'NavCore'],
    correctAnswer: 'React Navigation',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you style in React Native?',
    options: ['CSS', 'Tailwind', 'Stylesheet.create', 'SASS'],
    correctAnswer: 'Stylesheet.create',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which command starts an RN app?',
    options: ['npm dev', 'yarn init', 'npx react-native start', 'expo push'],
    correctAnswer: 'npx react-native start',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a component in RN?',
    options: ['View only', 'Function or class', 'Variable', 'HTML'],
    correctAnswer: 'Function or class',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is NOT a core component?',
    options: ['Text', 'Button', 'Flex', 'View'],
    correctAnswer: 'Flex',
  },
  {
    question: 'How to manage state?',
    options: ['Hooks', 'Router', 'Link', 'GetX'],
    correctAnswer: 'Hooks',
  },
];
